# JIRAYU TANCHAROEN

#### PROFILE (ABOUT ME)

2 years of work experience in junior full-stack software developer. I'm looking for job to open up new perspectives in my field, try learning new technology from experienced team members. That keep me continue to grow and improve my skills. So, I want to try many things to make myself don't get feel burnout. And also interested in research involving patients, elderly and disable persons that can bring technology to help them.

#### **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

C# Java Python SQL HTML/CSS JavaScript

Node.js (Basic)

Git Visual Studio | VS Code SQL Server

ASP.NET MVC Bootstrap Vue.js

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

**Mobile**: 086-549-1915

Email: 595021002000@mail.rmutk.ac.th

in Linkedin: <u>Jirayu Tancharoen</u>

Address: 419/547 Village No.10, Pracha Uthit Rd., Nai Khlong Bang Pla Kot, Phra Samut Chedi, Samut Prakan, 10290

#### **CERTIFICATE**









IC3 Microsoft Database
Certification Office Word Administration
- Global 2013 Fundamentals
Standard 5

Information Technology Passport xamination (IP)

## **MAIN INTERESTS**

Data Science DevOps Cybersecurity & Data Privacy

Digital Marketing BI (Business Intelligence)

Medical

# **EDUCATION HISTORY**

Rajamangala University of Technology Krungthep

University [Bachelor's degree] Bachelor of Science (Computer Science) | 2016 - 2019

Sarasas Pracha U-thit Pithayakarn School

Senior High School Class Math and English program | 2013 - 2015

## **WORK EXPERIENCE HISTORY**

ALT Plus X Co.,Ltd

Software Developer. (Full Stack) | June 2020 - August 2022

As a full-stack web developer with experience in ASP.NET MVC and C#, I have expertise in developing e-commerce and CMS web applications that meet the user's requirements. I conduct research and development to ensure the system's functionality and maintain the software code and supporting web applications post-deployment to production. With proficiency in using Agile in the software development life cycle, I collaborate with teams using Git for version control. My skills in front-end development, including HTML and CSS, and my knowledge of Transact-SQL (T-SQL) enable me to create high-quality and responsive web applications. Additionally, I have experience in developing payment functions using API of SCB to connect web applications with QR code payments.

Advanced Research Group Co., Ltd.

Intern. [AR Soft.]
| June 2019 - October 2019

With experience in system analysis, report development, and software testing, I am a skilled and detail-oriented professional with expertise in improving SQL queries and altering stored procedures in SQL Server databases to enhance server performance and user experience. My proficiency in Transact-SQL (T-SQL) and software system analysis, as well as report development using Jaspersoft iReport Designer tool, enables me to retrieve and format data for reports. Additionally, my manual testing skills, including generating test data, creating test cases and scenarios, and submitting defects, ensure the quality and accuracy of the developing system.